[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Scottish Gaelic name of the Loch Ness Monster?", "correct_answer": "Niseag", "incorrect_answers": ["Monstru", "Nillie", "Neska"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Taxonomy of vertebrates divides fishes into what two basic groups?", "correct_answer": "Jawed and jawless", "incorrect_answers": ["Gilled and non-gilled", "Mammalian and non-mammalian", "Nematodes and non-nematodes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This very popular opera singer from Australia lived 1861-1931. She had two foods named after her.", "correct_answer": "Nellie Melba", "incorrect_answers": ["Grace Toff", "Brigit Nielsen", "Jenny Lind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was Pepsi first made?", "correct_answer": "1890", "incorrect_answers": ["1780", "1870", "1980"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Clint Eastwood movie is a fictionalized account of the making of the movie, The African Queen?", "correct_answer": "White Hunter, Black Heart", "incorrect_answers": ["The Dark Continent", "Eighty Days in The Wild", "A Single Rifle Shot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the typical lifespan of the beagle?", "correct_answer": "12 years", "incorrect_answers": ["20 years", "15 years", "7 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Dale Evans married to?", "correct_answer": "Roy Rogers", "incorrect_answers": ["Buffalo Bill Cody", "Wild Bill Hickcock", "Gene Autry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following sauces provides the highest percent of calories from fat?", "correct_answer": "Arbys Light Mayonnaise Packet", "incorrect_answers": ["Burger Kings Honey Flavored Dipping Sauce", "Hardees Pancake Syrup", "McDonalds Barbeque Sauce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Comedian Ron White has a famous nickname that he mentions during the Blue Collar Comedy Tour and also on his albums,  What is that delicious nickname?", "correct_answer": "Tater Salad", "incorrect_answers": ["Tuna Salad", "Mac Salad", "Egg Salad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of designer Vivienne Westwoods fashion label?", "correct_answer": "Anglomania", "incorrect_answers": ["Westwooden", "Worlds End", "Vivere"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is no water found on any other planet besides Earth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this country, friends of the newly weds will do anything to make the first night as hard as possible.", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["Poland", "China", "Norway"]}]